have you ever after yourself this question what is my purpose
你有没有想过这个问题我的目的是什么
with so many opportunities that life has to offer and all is jobs and careers
生活提供了很多机会，而这一切都是工作和职业
it's quite difficult to the site now your wanted with ar life's society
现在您想要与AR Life's Society合作的网站很难
people chair make decisions at a very young age
主席在很小的时候就做出决定
about what were going to take most of the time
关于大部分时间将要花费的时间
children have no clue about what life is like and adulthood it becomes i wanted to
孩子们不知道生活是什么样，成年后我就不想了
endure grown up in fact many a dead don't even have color nou de
忍受着长大，事实上，许多死人甚至没有肤色
japanese invente t philosophy takes tikai which stands for reason for being the
日本发明哲学采用tikai，因为它是
key guy to help study terms when is that who want to make up for
帮助学习术语的关键人物是谁想要弥补
in the morning you know that very sing the weekend
早上你知道周末很唱歌
polar heart and soul into one become total immersion active, typical of such a man show
极地的心灵和灵魂融为一体，这就是典型的男人表演
that nothing else matters again in estate of flow ikitai helps to identify de
流动ikitai的财产再无其他问题，可以帮助您确定
necessary in radians to get into this flo's time and the make-up pursuit
弧度是进入这个flo的时间和化妆追求所必需的
sustainable and useful for the world
对世界可持续和有益
[Music]
[音乐]
many people work in the shop stiffness one who does the misery that way so
很多人在商店里僵硬地工作，那样苦难的人
shape with these activities or for sale juice and as on sunday nothing
通过这些活动或出售果汁来塑造自己，而在周日则一无所有
hi start think about this great for monday morning on which we have to dakar
嗨，开始想想周一早上的这个很棒，我们必须在达喀尔上班
even out of bed knowing that will spend and next week in hell
甚至下床知道会花时间，下周在地狱中
wanna be your life we ​​still experience this most al jeff for the weekend and and
想成为你的生活，我们仍然在周末经历这种最糟糕的事情，并且
soenens good start we pictures who countdown to the first break and
加快良好的开端，我们为谁倒计时到第一个休息时间拍照，
then and next and then the next and toe week and finally go stomach en
然后再下一个然后下一个和脚趾一周，最后去肚子
and two piet the process well this is a very enjoyable wtf think about doing
和两个很好的过程，这是一个非常愉快的wtf考虑做
something how hot is i this service tour cells and also their surroundings
我这项服务有多热，游览了牢房及其周围
and specially when i see other colleagues that actually enjoyed doing
特别是当我看到其他喜欢做事的同事时
and then top of that they're doing a great job and many people get measurable
最重要的是，他们做得很好，很多人都可以衡量
because of their jobs which in turn can lead to sirius health
因为他们的工作反而会导致天狼星的健康
problems like the pressure sammy van go as far as killing them
压力大的面包车之类的问题甚至会杀死他们
even I like the cannot buy with the feelings' of useless
即使无法用无用的感觉来购买
hopeless and so a cover nadia that there is a lot of us in a life but we've ever certain
毫无希望，所以这是一个秘密，我们生活中有很多人，但我们可以肯定
degree of control circumstances weekend right to change your position everywhere
周末的控制程度情况随时随地更改您的职位的权利
towards the situation and make-up green jump more enjoyable
迎合形势，绿色彩妆跃跃欲试
or week and ria 6 euros nature and the nature over surroundings and the likely
周和里亚尔6欧元的自然和周围的自然环境和可能
you come to the conclusion that it is better to find something different to
您得出的结论是，找到与之不同的东西更好
that the change who to make is to vault 'because who is not to change your mind
做出改变的人就是跳马，因为谁不会改变你的想法
set on the other hand you need to change your circumstances lucas louis doedel
另一方面，您需要更改环境
right things with the right mindset were able to enter estate of flow
具有正确心态的正确事物能够进入流动状态
ikitai helps to identify what is to write you tick for a shirt and individually
ikitai帮助您识别出要为您写一件衬衫的勾号，并逐一
so this person is able to get out of bed in the morning with s sense of purpose and
因此，这个人可以在早晨起床并有目的感，
therefore is able to work with almost no effort
因此几乎可以毫不费力地工作
well ok look consists of four die men chats firstly we need to pick
好吧，首先由四个die夫组成，我们需要选择
something that work looks like secondly it must be missing that will of
第二，它一定会丢失
surly the world don't show it and leslie
乖乖的世界不显示它，莱斯利
how hard to get paid let's talk about each die people
薪水有多难让我们谈谈每个死者
seperately was doing more could ever they won the skills at something would
他们会做更多的事情，他们会以某种方式赢得技能吗？
based on nurture and something will be based on nature
以养育为基础，某些事物将以自然为基础
for great part week and learn skills with you as we finish in Born Caractéristiques
大部分时间都在学习《生而死的灵魂》，并与您一起学习技巧
that with this point people suitable for your friend thanks for example
在这一点上，适合您朋友的人非常感谢
what does the francis see in a few motor skills
弗朗西斯在几项运动技能中看到了什么
mpv physical strength et cetera or the time's people focus on improving
mpv身体力量等等，还是那个时代的人们专注于提高
the things by bad die spencer whole life ribery nam cells
坏死的东西斯宾塞一辈子的肋骨南细胞
were getting the tanks by naturally good so white winter
在如此自然的冬天里得到了坦克
focus under ledger and test box skills so who came masters and the lucas like
专注于分类帐和测试框技能，这样谁来了大师和卢卡斯像
uzzo much energy to be coming mid saved best
将很多能量传到中间，以节省最大的精力
now he has opportunity to be great not to mention autoworld benefit
现在他有机会变得伟大，更不用说汽车世界的利益了
from as many fasting outro potential however according to the eighty guy
来自八十个家伙
philosophy the should be something that the world is not what you already address in one
哲学应该是世界不是你已经在其中解决的东西
minute to doing what would love to do this is
分钟想做的事情就是
very obvious what it will kind of rikki what we level of
很明显，我们将达到什么水平
skill can be measured this time engine is can or subjective and
这次可以衡量技能，引擎是可以还是主观的，
the bit complicated for example you might love to be a
有点复杂，例如，您可能想成为一名
full-time youtube content creator bitter might be some aspects of de
全职youtube内容创作者的苦恼可能是某些方面的问题
process you don't like and all my love editing videos
处理您不喜欢的视频以及我所有喜欢编辑的视频
righting script called filming in this case
这种情况下的补正脚本称为“拍摄”
filming the odds bottleneck now you can try to make filming more enjoyable
拍摄赔率瓶颈，现在您可以尝试使拍摄更加有趣
p'raps week and change our work flow go to give locations
欢庆一周，改变我们的工作流程，安排地点
zoey can still be in merced in the stage and experience of idleness
zoey仍然可以在舞台上闲逛，体验无所事事
mindset is ajar and drifter ride focus
心态半开，漂流者专注
were able to effortlessly goals tasks were necessary but that i don't like
能够轻松地实现目标任务是必要的，但我不喜欢
that much of course outsourcing is an option it is
当然，外包当然是一个选择
winner actively sizzle roll make stressful and two do see any way to
赢家积极发出嘶嘶声使人感到压力，而两个人确实看到了任何方法
develop a certain in giant damn it might be a better idea to find
发展一个该死的人，找到一个更好的主意
something els too expensive perhaps were just not interested in this
东西太贵了也许只是对此不感兴趣
field of skills leveling off what first race as at the end of the day
在今天结束的第一场比赛中达到水平的技能领域
theres no accounting for test such a thing probably much easier to just
没有考虑测试的事情，这样的事情可能要容易得多
listen to work out and letting you wish i decide where to go
听锻炼，让你希望我决定去哪里
three do what the world doesn't do it's all great one of the chairmen at work it out
三人做世界上没有做的事都是伟大的一位正在努力的主席
and what wants or to do what that is a ten of to quality guy picasso active
以及想要或做的事是毕加索活跃的十个人
t-shirt in a one way or another benefit world if they don't is simply a
T恤衫以一种或另一种方式造福于世界，如果他们不只是一种
luckily the nothing or the world can be a passion
幸运的是，虚无或世界可以成为激情
manager of flavors jobs at eye look down upon by some
风味工作经理眼中有些人看不起
people often highly important chinese [ __ ] on the trash someone so
人们常常非常重要的中国公鸡在垃圾桶上有人
factor cenk and who wouldn't be able to strive to society
人口统计以及谁将无法为社会奋斗
what keeps people clothes on the knife in fighting joint in the sound of jobs
是什么使人们在工作中与工人抗争
that absolutely liter add to discover what the world needs
绝对的升华可以发现世界的需求
weekend simply do such market research to find out of the current and the
周末只需做这样的市场研究，以找出当前和未来
moment oh i have a counters world for my
哦，我有一个专柜世界
wider perspective asking her cells howie of ar skill sets
询问她的单元格技能水平更高的观点
and make it a better place for generates money
并使其成为赚钱的好地方
sam argue that money is a tempo tent or shoot and effector
萨姆（Sam）辩称，金钱是拍拍子或拍子和表演者
the housing counter reality we see that money makes the world go round
住房逆境现实，我们看到钱使世界运转
it is getting old way weekend at the wales so to make an effort sustainable
周末在威尔士正在变老，以使可持续发展
and truly a reason for being themes generating side has nat ar
真正成为主题产生方的原因是
activities become more of a hobby there nothing wrong with a hobby of
活动变得越来越是一种爱好，而一项爱好却没有错
course however this also means that we'll show you might not like to pay the
当然，这也意味着我们将向您表明您可能不愿意支付
bills and for that sacrifice the with george over
账单，并为此牺牲了乔治
time and energy for santing were not passionate about
浪费时间和精力不热衷于
and do the csi life's mission as well simon isa form of energy
并完成csi life的使命simon is a energy of an energy
dot view as in her pursuit is now even dressed the for those mansions of epica
她追求的点状视图现在甚至可以装扮成史诗般的豪宅了
essential pressure track houthi's die mentions relate to each other and how a
Houthi的死讯中提到的基本压力追踪彼此相关，以及
combination of them do not form idea how I do some wheel off and on
他们的组合不形成想法我如何做一些轮转
it will be good who have a passion what the special is insufficient to be and if
有激情的人会很好，这是什么特别的东西是不够的，如果
i cry because it could very well be something that the world a thousand cannot or
我哭是因为这很可能是世界上一千个不能或不可以的东西
save and destructive to our environment also bring it to generate money or evil
拯救和破坏我们的环境也使它产生金钱或邪恶
costs money jetbeam passionate about something is part of genetics do it
花费金钱对某些事物充满热情的射束是遗传学的一部分
wheel off and you don't want to be a girl with a mission though pay is one
滚开，你不想成为一个有使命的女孩，尽管报酬是一个
technique i cry because you might not be good at
我哭泣的技术，因为你可能不擅长
and nat earning a time doing it jets sinar activities as en mission is one
纳特（Nat）在做这件事时会抽出一些鼻窦活动，因为宣教是其中之一
ingredient for aims for be one who does something new world
目标是成为做新世界的人
get paid for profound evocation what does that mean i'd be like what would
因深厚的激励而获得报酬，这意味着我会像什么
you and that for you did not necessarily and that's why there vocation maybe
你和那对你来说并不一定，这就是为什么有职业的原因
something that the world the moment and that we value for sense of duty
就是这个世界，我们珍惜责任感的东西
what your name is absolutely lee do it like this
你叫什么名字李绝对是这样子的
evocation alone is a technique that leslie do what regret and those were
莱斯利（Leslie）独自做的一项技术就是后悔，而那些
paid for risk always profession teacher minutes world and not sit and the wheel off
为风险付出的钱总是职业老师记录世界，而不是坐着和滚开
what we do i'm not necessarily some people hate to
我们要做的事情不一定是某些人讨厌的
their profession and some profession sorry from destructive to the world so
他们的职业和某些职业从毁灭性的世界走向遗憾
i professional pay is a unique idea what
我的专业薪酬是一个绝妙的主意
makes and ikitai is the combination and or all for those mentions
品牌和ikitai是组合，或所有这些提及
this means at and reason for being includes a passion ambition
这意味着在和存在的理由包括激情的野心
evocation and the professor who for all the ingredients at facilities to engage
激发和教授参与设施中所有要素的参与
in a yard pursuit that we love to get up for in
在我们喜欢站起来的院子里追求
the morning and only love it would you it's easy to emerge or even in the and
早晨，只有爱，它很容易出现，甚至在和
gettin estate of flow de secret life and online euro nature
秘密生活和在线欧元自然界的开始
with the nature of our and fire with an optimal interplay between strapless
与我们的天性和火力之间无肩带之间的最佳互动
or even and whether your own should be nothing so brave
甚至，甚至你自己都不应该如此勇敢
effortlessly chose the do with cold is how we can be
毫不费力地选择与寒冷做的事
translated and effortless action they are central to remember that were
翻译和毫不费力的动作，他们是记住这些的核心
looking for is not set in stone many factors play a role in the siding
寻找不是一成不变的，许多因素在壁板上发挥作用
what is eps in a constantly changing world
在不断变化的世界中，eps是什么
remaining in this flo's time at least two continuous we limit we depth and find you
在这个时间段中至少剩余两个连续的时间，我们限制深度并找到您
a position or in the high iq guy for that is a strong and active
一个职位或高智商的人是一个坚强而活跃的人
entity that changes with the flow of time thank you for watching
随着时间的流逝而变化的实体感谢您的观看
[Music]
[音乐]